Guide to the Sara M. Evans Papers, 1959-2005 RL.10161
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Audiocassettes Series, 1972-1989; 1; 256 items
  - Heather Booth, Vivian Rothstein, 1973 July 10; 3
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0092)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0093)
  - Vivian Rothstein, Richie Rothstein and Paul Booth, Chicago, 1973 July 12; 4
    - Cassette original (Box 31, Audio-cassette RL10161-CS-0004)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0093)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0094)
  - Paul Booth, Barbara Easton, Berkeley, 1973 July 15; 5
    - Cassette original (Box 31, Audio-cassette RL10161-CS-0005)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0094)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0095)
  - Barbara Easton and Mimi Feingold, undated; 6
    - Cassette original (Box 31, Audio-cassette RL10161-CS-0006)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0095)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0096)
  - Mimi Feingold and Pam Allen, 1973 July 17; 7
    - Cassette original (Box 31, Audio-cassette RL10161-CS-0007)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0097)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0098)
  - Pam Allen, undated; 8
    - Cassette original (Box 31, Audio-cassette RL10161-CS-0008)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0098)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0099)
  - Leni Wildflower, San Jose, CA, 1973 July 18; 9
    - Cassette original (Box 31, Audio-cassette RL10161-CS-0009)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0099)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0100)
  - Leni Wildflower, Paul Potter and Linda Daucher, San Francisco, CA, 1973 July 19; 10
    - Cassette original (Box 31, Audio-cassette RL10161-CS-0010)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0100)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0101)
  - Linda Daucher and Joan Jordan, San Francisco, 1973 July 19; 11
    - Cassette original (Box 31, Audio-cassette RL10161-CS-0011)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0101)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0102)
  - Joan Jordan, undated; 12
    - Cassette original (Box 31, Audio-cassette RL10161-CS-0012)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0102)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0103)
  - Vicki Gabrener, Atlanta, GA, 1973 June 29; 13
    - Cassette original (Box 31, Audio-cassette RL10161-CS-0013)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0104)
  - Leah Johnson Wise, Atlanta, GA, 1973 June 29; 14
    - Cassette original (Box 31, Audio-cassette RL10161-CS-0014)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0105)
  - Nan Grogan, Atlanta, GA, 1973 June 28; 15
    - Cassette original (Box 31, Audio-cassette RL10161-CS-0015)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0106)
  - Sue Thrasher, Atlanta, GA, 1973 June 30; 16
    - Cassette original (Box 31, Audio-cassette RL10161-CS-0016)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0107)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0108)
  - Sue Thrasher and Cathy Cade, Berkeley, CA, 1973 June 21; 17
    - Cassette original (Box 31, Audio-cassette RL10161-CS-0017)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0108)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0109)
  - Cathy Cade, undated; 18
    - Cassette original (Box 32, Audio-cassette RL10161-CS-0018)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0109)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0110)
  - Sydney Halpern and Anne Wells, Berkeley, CA, 1973 July 20-21; 19
    - Cassette original (Box 32, Audio-cassette RL10161-CS-0019)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0110)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0111)
  - Anne Wells and Mary King, Washington, DC, 1972 July 24; 20
    - Cassette original (Box 32, Audio-cassette RL10161-CS-0020)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0111)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0112)
  - Mary King and Linda Carcione, 1973 July 25; 21
    - Cassette original (Box 32, Audio-cassette RL10161-CS-0021)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0113)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0114)
  - Gwen Patton, Washington, DC, 1973 June 20; 22
    - Cassette original (Box 32, Audio-cassette RL10161-CS-0022)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0114)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0115)
  - Jean Walton, Washington, DC, 1973 June 21; 23
    - Cassette original (Box 32, Audio-cassette RL10161-CS-0023)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0115)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0116)
  - Charlotte Bunch, Washington, DC, 1973 June 21; 24
    - Cassette original (Box 32, Audio-cassette RL10161-CS-0024)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0116)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0117)
  - Marcia Kopit and Alice Wolfson, 1973 June 22; 25
    - Cassette original (Box 32, Audio-cassette RL10161-CS-0025)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0117)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0118)
  - Betty Garmon and Jimmy Garrett, Washington, DC, 1973 July 26; 26
    - Cassette original (Box 32, Audio-cassette RL10161-CS-0026)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0118)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0119)
  - Betty Garmon and Jean Wiley, Washington, DC, 1973 July 26; 27
    - Cassette original (Box 32, Audio-cassette RL10161-CS-0027)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0119)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0120)
  - Fay Bellamy, Atlanta, GA, 1973 June 29; 28
    - Cassette original (Box 32, Audio-cassette RL10161-CS-0028)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0120)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0121)
  - Susan Brownmiller and Kathy Sarachild (Kathie Amatniek), New York, New York, 1973 July 27; 29
    - Cassette original (Box 32, Audio-cassette RL10161-CS-0029)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0121)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0122)
  - Kathie Sarachild (Kathie Amatniek) and Carol Hanish, New York, New York, 1973 July 28; 30
    - Cassette original (Box 32, Audio-cassette RL10161-CS-0030)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0122)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0123)
  - Carol Hanish and Rachael Fructer, Brooklyn, NY, 1973 July 29; 31
    - Cassette original (Box 32, Audio-cassette RL10161-CS-0031)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0123)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0124)
  - Rachel Fructer and Naomi Weisstein, New Providence, New York, 1973 July 30; 32
    - Cassette original (Box 32, Audio-cassette RL10161-CS-0032)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0124)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0125)
  - Naomi Weisstein and Ella Baker, New York, New York, 1973 July 31; 33
    - Cassette original (Box 32, Audio-cassette RL10161-CS-0033)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0126)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0127)
  - Ella Baker (no audio), undated; 34
    - Cassette original (Box 32, Audio-cassette RL10161-CS-0034)
  - Mike Zagarell and Lois Chaffee, New York, New York, 1973 August 1; 35
    - Cassette original (Box 32, Audio-cassette RL10161-CS-0035)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0127)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0128)
  - Lois Chaffee, Marya Levenson, Cambridge, MA, 1973 August 4; 36
    - Cassette original (Box 32, Audio-cassette RL10161-CS-0036)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0128)
  - Marya Levenson and Dorothy Burlage, Cambridge, MA, 1973 August 5; 37
    - Cassette original (Box 32, Audio-cassette RL10161-CS-0037)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0129)
  - Dorothy Burlage, Danny Schecter and Roz Baxendall, Truro, MA, 1973 August 6; 38
    - Cassette original (Box 32, Audio-cassette RL10161-CS-0038)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0130)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0131)
  - Roz Baxendall and Linda Gordon, undated; 39
    - Cassette original (Box 32, Audio-cassette RL10161-CS-0039)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0131)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0132)
  - Linda Gordon and Anne Froines, Somerville, MA, 1973 August 7; 40
    - Cassette original (Box 32, Audio-cassette RL10161-CS-0040)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0132)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0133)
  - Anne Froines and Beth Reisen, Boston, MA, 1973 August 7; 41
    - Cassette original (Box 32, Audio-cassette RL10161-CS-0041)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0133)
  - Beth Reisen and Howard Zinn, Boston, MA, undated; 42
    - Cassette original (Box 32, Audio-cassette RL10161-CS-0042)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0134)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0135)
  - Howard Zinn, Boston, MA, 1973 August 7; 43
    - Cassette original (Box 32, Audio-cassette RL10161-CS-0043)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0135)
  - Dana Densmore and Beth Oglesby, Cambridge, MA, 1973 August 7; 44
    - Cassette original (Box 32, Audio-cassette RL10161-CS-0044)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0136)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0137)
  - Joanie Rabinowitz, undated; 45
    - Cassette original (Box 32, Audio-cassette RL10161-CS-0045)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0137)
  - Sandra "Casey" Cason, New York, New York, 1977 July 13; 46
    - Cassette original (Box 32, Audio-cassette RL10161-CS-0046)
    - Cassette original (Box 32, Audio-cassette RL10161-CS-0047)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0137)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0138)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0139)
  - Craig, 1974 March; 47
    - Cassette original (Box 32, Audio-cassette RL10161-CS-0048)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0139)
  - Harry Boyte, 1973 March 12; 48
    - Cassette original (Box 32, Audio-cassette RL10161-CS-0049)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0139)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0140)
  - Heather Booth, Chicago, IL, 1972 November 5; 49
    - Cassette original (Box 32, Audio-cassette RL10161-CS-0050)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0141)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0142)
  - Staughton and Alice, Chicago, IL, 1972 November 4; 50
    - Cassette original (Box 32, Audio-cassette RL10161-CS-0051)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0142)
  - Joan Tighe, Boston, MA, 1981 June 19; 51
    - Cassette original (Box 32, Audio-cassette RL10161-CS-0052)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0143)
  - Heather Booth, Chicago, IL, 1981 July 15; 52
    - Cassette original (Box 33, Audio-cassette RL10161-CS-0053)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0144)
  - Sally Martino Fisher and Francine Moccio, Brooklyn, New York, 1983 April 21; 53
    - Cassette original (Box 33, Audio-cassette RL10161-CS-0054)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0144)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0145)
  - Jan Peterson, undated; 54
    - Cassette original (Box 33, Audio-cassette RL10161-CS-0055)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0145)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0146)
  - Janice Blood and Janet Silcer, undated; 55
    - Cassette original (Box 33, Audio-cassette RL10161-CS-0056)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0147)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0148)
  - Ann Ladke, Chicago, IL, 1983 April 18-21; 56
    - Cassette original (Box 33, Audio-cassette RL10161-CS-0057)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0148)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0149)
  - Beata Walsh, Chicago, IL, 1981 July 15; 57
    - Cassette original (Box 33, Audio-cassette RL10161-CS-0058)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0149)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0150)
  - Joyce Miller, New York, New York, 1983 February 7; 58
    - Cassette original (Box 33, Audio-cassette RL10161-CS-0059)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0150)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0151)
  - Darlene Stille, Chicago, IL, 1981 July 15; 59
    - Cassette original (Box 33, Audio-cassette RL10161-CS-0060)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0151)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0152)
  - Kathy Rand, Chicago, IL, 1983 June 16-17; 60
    - Cassette original (Box 33, Audio-cassette RL10161-CS-0061)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0152)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0153)
  - Jean Hoffenkamp, Chicago, IL, 1983 June 16; 61
    - Cassette original (Box 33, Audio-cassette RL10161-CS-0062)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0153)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0154)
  - Andrea Gunderson, Chicago, IL, 1983 April 17; 62
    - Cassette original (Box 33, Audio-cassette RL10161-CS-0063)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0154)
  - Janet Schumacher, Chicago, IL, 1983 June 17; 63
    - Cassette original (Box 33, Audio-cassette RL10161-CS-0064)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0155)
  - Ellen Cassidy, Bryn Mawr, PA, 1981 July 11; 64
    - Cassette original (Box 33, Audio-cassette RL10161-CS-0065)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0156)
  - Olga Madar, Detroit, MI, 1982 December 10; 65
    - Cassette original (Box 33, Audio-cassette RL10161-CS-0066)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0157)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0158)
  - Dorothy Haener, Detroit, MI, 1983 January 21; 66
    - Cassette original (Box 33, Audio-cassette RL10161-CS-0067)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0158)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0159)
  - Anne Trugy, Minneapolis, MN, 1977 December 8; 67
    - Cassette original (Box 33, Audio-cassette RL10161-CS-0068)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0159)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0160)
  - Addie Wyatt, Chicago, IL, 1983 June 15; 68
    - Cassette original (Box 33, Audio-cassette RL10161-CS-0069)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0160)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0161)
  - Anne Ladky, Chicago, IL, 1983 June 16-17; 69
    - Cassette original (Box 33, Audio-cassette RL10161-CS-0070)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0161)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0162)
  - Day Piercy, Chicago, IL, 1981 July 16; 70
    - Cassette original (Box 33, Audio-cassette RL10161-CS-0071)
    - Cassette original (Box 33, Audio-cassette RL10161-CS-0072)
    - Cassette original (Box 33, Audio-cassette RL10161-CS-0073)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0162)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0163)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0164)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0165)
  - Marie Bueno, Brooklyn, NY, 1983 April 4-21; 71
    - Cassette original (Box 33, Audio-cassette RL10161-CS-0074)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0165)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0166)
  - Jan Peterson and Jean Kowalsky, Brookly, NY, 1983 April 20; 72
    - Cassette original (Box 33, Audio-cassette RL10161-CS-0075)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0166)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0167)
  - Sally Martino Fisher, Brooklyn, NY, 1983 April 20; 73
    - Cassette original (Box 33, Audio-cassette RL10161-CS-0076)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0167)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0168)
  - Alice Quinn, Brooklyn, NY, 1983 April 20; 74
    - Cassette original (Box 33, Audio-cassette RL10161-CS-0077)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0168)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0169)
  - Frances Allen, Brooklyn, NY, 1983 April 22; 75
    - Cassette original (Box 33, Audio-cassette RL10161-CS-0078)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0169)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0170)
  - Ione Biggs and Ann Hill, Bryn Mawr, PA, 1981 July 11; 76
    - Cassette original (Box 33, Audio-cassette RL10161-CS-0079)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0170)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0171)
  - Don Bender (neighborhood movement) and Gene Guerrero with Thrusher (sex roles), Atlanta, GA, 1977 March 25; 77
    - Cassette original (Box 33, Audio-cassette RL10161-CS-0080)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0172)
  - Women and the Student Nonviolent Coordinating Committee (SNCC), From the SNCC reunion, Spring, 1988, 78
    - Cassette original (Box 33, Audio-cassette RL10161-CS-0081)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0173)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0174)
  - The world of letters with Sara Evans, Iowa City, IA, 1980 November 13; 79
    - Cassette original (Box 33, Audio-cassette RL10161-CS-0082)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0174)
  - Leo Laporte, 1989 June 28; 80
    - Cassette original (Box 33, Audio-cassette RL10161-CS-0083)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0174)
  - Conversation with Mildred Jeffry, December 9, 1982, 1982 December 9; 81
    - Cassette original (Box 33, Audio-cassette RL10161-CS-0084)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0175)
  - National Council of Negro Women (NCNW), Brookly, NY, 1983 February 5; 82
    - Cassette original (Box 33, Audio-cassette RL10161-CS-0085)
    - Cassette original (Box 33, Audio-cassette RL10161-CS-0086)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0176)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0177)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0178)
  - Feminist Roundtable, 83
    - Cassette original (Box 33, Audio-cassette RL10161-CS-0087)
    - Compact disc use copy (Box 47, Audio-disc RL10161-CD-0178)
- Lectures, 1974-2000; 2 boxes
  This series contains Evans' lectures given outside the University of Minnesota, retained in their original order, organized alphabetically by the place they were given.
  - Lectures, A-B (Box 39)
  - Lectures, C-D (Box 39)
  - Lectures, F-K (Box 39)
  - Lectures, L-N (Box 39)
  - Lectures, O-P (Box 40)
  - Lectures, R-T (Box 40)
  - Lectures, Wage Justice (Box 40)
  - Lectures, Wayne-Winona (Box 40)
  - Lectures, Women in the 20th Century (Box 40)
- Correspondence, Projects, Spirituality, and Miscellany, 1962-2007; 5 boxes
  This series contains professional correspondence, project files, materials relating to Christian feminism, Evans' student papers, student activist documentation, and miscellaneous files
  - Kellogg National Fellowship Program, 1986 (Box 41)
  - Kellogg National Fellowship Program, 1982-1986 (Box 41)
  - Vietnam summer, undated (Box 41)
  - Correspondence, 1971-1990, 4 folders (Box 41)
  - Correspondence, 1990-1999 (Box 42)
  - Rajender settlement report, 1990 (Box 42)
  - Articles, notes, Organization of American Historians (OAH), 1981-1982 (Box 42)
  - Oral history project on Southern women, 1973-1976 (Box 42)
  - C.P. Gilman New American Movement (NAM), 1973-1975 (Box 42)
  - Ruth Pollack, 1991-1995 (Box 42)
  - Girl Scout documentary, 1999 (Box 42)
  - World Student Christian Foundation (WSCF) women's history project, 1996-1998 (Box 42)
  - Teaching awards ceremony, 2005 (Box 43)
  - Graduate school commencement ceremony, 2005 (Box 43)
  - Retention file, 1989 (Box 43)
  - Tenure at the University of Minnesota, 1997 (Box 43)
  - Photos of Gerda Lerner event, 1990 (Box 43)
  - OAH information, 1996-1997 (Box 43)
  - Journeys That Opened Up the World, 2003-2006 (Box 43)
  - Women's studies classes, 1973 (Box 43)
  - Dissertation, 1972-1973 (Box 43)
  - Interviews and notes, 1979 (Box 43)
  - Students for a Democratic Society (SDS) literature, 1962-1963 (Box 43)
  - Student papers, 1966-1970 (Box 43)
  - Re-Imagining Conference (feminist theology), 2000-2003, 2 folders (Box 44)
  - Re-Imagining Conference (feminist theology), 1994-2003, 3 folders (Box 44)
  - Group 22 reunion, 1989-2002 (Box 44)
  - Articles, 1992-1996 (Box 44)
  - Lighthouse report, 2004 (Box 44)
  - Sacred journey, 2007 (Box 44)
  - World Student Christian Federation, 1997-2001 (Box 45)
  - Rockefeller Foundation grants, 1976-1989 (Box 45)
  - Sarah Lawrence institute, 1973-1977 (Box 45)
  - Duke classwork, 1963 (Box 45)
  - Socialist feminism policy papers, 1972 (Box 45)
  - University of Chicago draft policies, 1966 (Box 45)
  - Personal miscellanea, 1977 and undated (Box 45)
  - Dakota mission tabulation sheets, undated (Box 45)